Marcus Vinicius dos Santos



marcusdj18@gmail.com



47991015600



linkedin.com/in/engenheiromarcus



https://engmarcus.github.io/resumeMarcus/

Summary

Passionate, creative and results-oriented technology professional with over a decade of experience in the field. Fascinated with contributing to people development, providing business improvements, all with the aim of making the business or idea grow aggressively.

I am graduated in Computer Engineering and always in constant study currently in Front and Back-End development, I have experience in:

DevOps (Windows and Linux), Development and Maintenance of systems at different levels, Creation of BACK-END and FRONT-END web and Mobile systems. (Reactjs, ReactNative, NodeJs, PHP, Mysql)

In my spare time, I enjoy tasting whiskeys, studying new technologies, traveling and hiking outdoors.

https://engmarcus.github.io/resumeMarcus/ (em Desenvolvimento)

Experience



Development Analyst

Grupo Belem

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Working with Front-End and Back-End Technologies, integrating and developing new solutions using REACTJS, REACT NATIVE, JAVASCRIPT, HTML,CSS,TYPESCRIPT, NODEJS,MYSQL,PHP

Support analyst

Company Sistemas

Mar 2021 - Sep 2021 (7 months)

responsible for initiating the integration between the offered system and new functionalities, for this purpose started the creation of the BACK-END in Python for data integration with dashboard platforms

Teacher

CENAIC SÃO BENTO DO SUL

Mar 2019 - Feb 2020 (1 year)

IT analyst

MicroBussines

Apr 2013 - Dec 2018 (5 years 9 months)

In the area of public tenders, responsible for the technical area:

Technical verifications of public notices

Maintenance and assembly of computers, servers and storage

Generation of partnerships with equipment manufacturers

IT specialist

MicroBusiness

Apr 2013 - Dec 2018 (5 years 9 months)

Instructor

Cenaic

Jan 2010 - Jan 2013 (3 years 1 month)

Course Instructor:

programming and games

3D animation and modeling

Assembly Maintenance

typing

technical english

Computing

Informatica Kids

Education



Bachelor in Computer Engineering, Computer engineering 2013 - 2018

Senac Brasil

Computer Technician, Computer/Hardware Technology 2006 - 2007

Licenses & Certifications

- Bachelor in Computer Engineering UniSociesc Centro Universitário
- Conectar do Discover Rocketseat 1d76e20f-58e8-4d7f-8db0-2090547b7c4e
- Fundamentar do Discover Rocketseat 89ecc2c1-5047-434e-8aab-3ee365476b3c
- Trilha Especializar do Discover Rocketseat 2f5a6ff5-e616-4b6c-8f43-572197048e76

Skills

Oracle SQL Developer • typegraphql • PHP • React.js • React Native • Node.js • MySQL • JSON • JavaScript • TypeScript